Oye, oye, oye.
Veronica thinks
it's best for both of you
if you stay away.
If you’re playing her secretary,
then tell her
I know your little dirty secret.
This is good!
I need to remember the name.
Honey!
What are you doing here?
You wanted to join us?
I think that's enough.
I'm afraid
that a guy like you couldn’t afford
this bottle.
What?
I said that's enough.
What are you doing?
We're leaving.
Hey! Anthony!
What?
Don't touch me!
You are...
What gives you the right?
And that's how Mason Powell
handle things.
And that's sexy, if I may say so.
This is for your phone.
And for keeping your mouth shut.
Hey, it's kidnaping.
Is there any security here?
Anthony!
Anthony, help me!